原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     苏小黛   吃冰棒   一只虾
翻译     TheWalkingNerd   静妹粒   酸奶
校对     小酸奶
时间轴     西查   没有影子
后期     8T
总监     小酸奶
双峰
第三季第十集
米里亚姆
Miriam.
走开  理查德
Go away, Richard!
听我说  我只想跟你谈谈
Hey, hey, I just want to talk to you.
我已经告诉警察了
I already told the police
你是撞了那孩子
it was you who ran over the little boy.
-你已经告诉警察了  -对
- You already told the police? - Yes!
别过来  理查德
Stay away, Richard!
你还告诉别人了吗
Tell anybody else?
没有
No.
但我不知道你怎么还没被捕
But I don't know why you're not arrested,
所以我还写了一封信
so I also wrote a letter.
什么意思  信
What do you mean, a letter?
我给警长写了一封信
I wrote a letter to the sheriff,
杜鲁门警长  而且寄出去了
Sheriff Truman, and mailed it,
把我知道的都告诉他了
telling him everything I know,
我还说  如果我出了什么事
and I told him if anything happens to me,
一定是你干的  所以  就是这样
it was you who did it, so... there!
今天寄的吗
Sent that letter today?
没错
That's right.
过来
Come here!
过来  过来
Come here! Come here!
快过来
Come here!
闭嘴
Shut up!
-查德  -怎么了
- Chad. - What's up?
听着  那贱人米里亚姆
Listen, that little bitch Miriam
今天给警长寄了一封信
sent a letter to the sheriff today.
你得截住那狗娘养的
You got to intercept that motherfucker.
那可没那么容易  理查德
Oh, that ain't gonna be real easy, Richard.
你真是个懦夫
What a pussy you are!
别让那信落到警长手里
Don't let that fucking letter get to the sheriff,
你这混蛋  不然我让你也不好过
you chickenshit, or I'll fuck you up bad.
这要求可不容易办到  伙计
You're asking a lot there, pal.
我试试
I'll try.
光试试可不够  混蛋
You do more than try, fuck face.
我要走了
I'm taking off.
*从这山谷中*
*From this valley*
*他们说*
*They say*
*你将要离去*
*You are leaving*
*我会想念你的明眸*
* I will miss your bright eyes *
*以及你的甜笑*
*And sweet smile*
*他们说*
*For they say*
*你将带走*
*You are taking*
*阳光*
*The sunshine*
*那将照亮*
*That will brighten*
*来坐到我身边*
*Come and sit by my side*
*亲爱的*
*Little darling*
*别犹豫*
*Do not hasten*
*跟我道别*
*To bid me adieu*
*只要记得*
*Just remember*
*红河谷...*
*That Red River Valley...*
该死
Fuck!
我要把这些破玩意儿都扔出去
I will throw all of this shit out the window.
别他妈跟我说话了
Quit fucking speaking to me,
我他妈干啥或者不干啥
and what I do or don't fucking do
轮不到你来管
doesn't concern you.
简直是他妈的噩梦
It's a fucking nightmare.
不用我废话废话
I don't tell you shit
比如你他妈为什么不要求加薪
like why the fuck you don't ask for a raise.
话说回来  你到底能赚多少钱
How much money do you make, anyways?
你连最低时薪都挣不到
You barely make minimum wage!
我们根本负担不起这破地方
We can't even afford this shit hole.
不用我多说  把这破地方打扫干净
I don't tell you to clean this fucking place up!
你他妈敢动一下试试
Don't you fucking move.
你他妈...
Don't you fucking...
听我说  听我说
Listen to me. Listen to me.
别他妈用那无辜的样子看着我
Don't you give me that fucking innocent look.
我很清楚你做了什么
I know exactly what you did.
一清二楚
Exactly what you did.
你他妈...该死
You fuck... Ah, shit...
-我伤到你了  -坎迪
- I've hurt you! - Candie!
什么情况  怎么回事
What happened? What happened?
很抱歉  对不起
I'm so sorry! I'm sorry!
我的天  罗德尼  让我看看
Jesus! Rodney, let me see that.
-没事的  -让我看看
- It's all right! - Let me see this.
坎迪
Candie!
你都干了些什么  坎迪
What the fuck did you do, Candie?
-放手  放手  -放开我
- Get off. Get off! - Keep off of me!
坎迪  你都...
Candie! What the...
-老天啊  -放轻松  放轻松
- Jesus Christ. - Easy. Easy.
没事了  没事了
It's all right. It's all right.
没事的
It's gonna be all right.
出了点血
Ah, it's bleeding a little bit.
没事吧  流血了吗
Is it all right? Is it bleeding?
我手上有血  在流血吗
I got blood. Is it bleeding?
放开他  坎迪  坎迪  坎迪
Get away, Candie! Candie! Candie!
坎迪  坎迪  让...
Candie! Candie, let--
道吉  请坐
Dougie, have a seat.
好吧  那就站着检查吧
All right. I'll, uh, examine you standing up.
总之  我说过了  本医生
Anyway, as I told you, Dr. Ben,
他是上个星期开始这样的
it started last week
道吉消失了三天后回来就这样了
when Dougie disappeared for three days.
他都错过了桑尼·吉姆的生日派对
He missed Sonny Jim's birthday party,
我们为这个派对准备了六个月
which we'd been planning for six months,
然后他就突然从赌场回了家
and then he shows up straight from the casino.
你知道他的赌博恶习
You know about his gambling problems
还有酗酒
and then the drinking,
酗酒和赌博相互滋长
and the drinking feeds the gambling and vice versa,
整件事就是个恶性循环
and the whole thing is just a downward spiral.
道吉  你最近有在健身吗
Dougie, have you been exercising?
健身
Exercising.
还有  你瘦了很多
You have lost a good amount of weight, also.
-还有  -咱们继续
- Also. - Go on.
他就是...  我说不好...
Well, he's just... I don't know...
有点行为奇怪
acting peculiar.
奇怪
Peeee-culiar.
不  别动  道吉  我得听听这里
Uh, no, no, no. Dougie, I got to listen here.
道吉  别动
Dougie. No.
听我说  不行  道吉  道吉
Listen. No, Dougie. Dougie.
好了
Okay.
这个...
Well...
道吉  你的心肺功能看上去非常棒
Dougie, your heart and lungs sound fantastic,
那我们来量量血压
so let's check your blood pressure.
他体重减了多少
How much weight has he lost?
我觉得他瘦了很多
I-I-I think he's lost a lot of weight.
不过是好的那种
In a good way.
没错
Oh, yes.
道吉  上次我见你时  你还是挺超重的
Dougie, last time I saw you, you were quite overweight.
重
Weight?
是的  超重  对身体不好
Yes. Overweight and, uh, headed for trouble.
100/70
One ten over 70.
你身体好极了
Perfect.
简直惊人
Remarkable.
坎迪  坎迪  我没事了
Candie. Candie, I'm fine.
我挺好的  没事...
I-I'm okay. It's...
保罗  下一步我们怎么做
Paul, where do we go next?
掷骰子  希娜
Roll the dice, Sheena.
本地新闻
-本地新闻  -本地新闻为您报道
- Local news! - Well, in local news,
今日市区酒店发生的重大事件
major excitement at a downtown hotel today...
布拉德  布拉德
Brad. Brad!
-怎么了  -艾克被抓了
- Huh? - They got Ike.
"长钉"施泰特勒
"The Spike" Stadtler.
不是吧
No shit.
那个混蛋
That asshole.
艾克终于捅出大篓子了
Ike finally stepped on his dick.
布拉德  记得提醒我取消给艾克设置的提醒
Brad, remind me to call off that hit on Ike.
给我们省了不少事  太好了
Save us a whack o' dough. Nice!
施泰特勒涉嫌多起与黑帮有关的谋杀案
Stadtler is a suspect in a number of gangland-related murders,
包括昨天的一起
including an attempt just yesterday
企图谋杀本地商人
on the life of this local businessman,
道吉·琼斯先生的案子
Mr. Douglas Jones.
受害者  才不是
Victim? Oh, no.
那个人看起来一点也不像受害者
That guy didn't act like any victim.
道格拉斯·琼斯  他的动作如眼镜蛇般迅速
Douglas Jones, he moved like a cobra.
我只看到了一个影子闪过
All I saw was a blur.
然后我们下了楼  我正牵着道吉
Then we came down, and I was holding on to Dougie.
我们在和平常一样说话
We were having a regular conversation
谈论着他的钱和保险  然后
about his money and insurance and-and--
别  道吉  不能这么做
No, Dougie, don't do that.
我们只是路过
And we were just walking along,
聊着私事  我拉着他
minding our own business, and I held on to him,
然后  不知从哪窜出来一个人径直朝向我们
and then, out of nowhere, someone came right at us,
手里拿着把枪
pointing a gun at my husband,
我们就...  道吉
and we were just-- Dougie!
他开始...  枪掉了
He wa--he started-- the gun went off,
吓死我了  也吓坏了我的道吉
and it scared me, and my Dougie,
他给他喉咙上来了个漂亮的空手切
he gave him a good old karate chop in the throat,
我还打了他几拳
and I punched him a couple times.
我说  "你少敢碰...  放开他
I said, "Don't you touch-- just get off him!
放开他"  然后我们...  他就跑了
Get off him!" And then we--he ran off!
我不知道他从哪跑出来的  这一切...
I don't know where he went, and it was... it was just--
这里暂停一下
Freeze it there.
你只是在尽本职工作  对吗  道吉
You just took care of business, right, Doug--
这就是我们的头彩先生  罗德尼
That's our Mr. Jackpots, Rodney.
我觉得也是  布拉德利
I think you're right, Bradley.
结果
Turns out,
我们的琼斯先生
our Mr. Jones
其实是...
is actually...
琼斯先生
Mr. Jones.
这世界真小
What a fuckin' world.
你...
How...
怎么可能会...
can you ever...
爱我...
love me...
我对你做了这么过分的事
...after what-what I-- what I did?
道吉
Dougie.
你觉得我迷人吗
Do you find me attractive?
你觉得吗
Well? Do you?
我觉得你很迷人
I find you attractive.
道吉
Dougie.
道吉  真棒
Dougie! Oh, yes.
好爽  道吉
Oh. Yes, Dougie.
好爽
Yes.
道吉
Dougie.
道吉  道吉
Dougie! Dougie!
Dougie. Dougie.
道吉
Dougie!
道吉  道吉
Dougie! Dougie!
道吉
Dougie!
Dougiiieee!
道吉
Dougie.
Oh, Dougie.
道吉
Dougie?
我爱你
I love you.
Love you.
道吉
Dougie.
这些破事又上演了
And the fucks are at it again!
去你妈的  你背叛了你选择要帮助的人
Fuck you who betray the people you were elected to help!
对这些怪物来说我们就像无助的羔羊
We're sheep to these monsters,
他们一点也不在乎我们
and they don't give a shit!
等着羊毛丰盈
We grow our wool,
当我们刚能自保温暖
and just when we're getting warm,
他们就会拿着电动剪刀
they come along with their electric clippers
把我们的羊毛剃个精光
and shear our wool off,
我们只是一群赤裸裸的尖叫着的小杂碎
and we're just naked, screaming little fucks!
没有羊毛留给我们
No wool for us!
饥寒交迫
Freezing and hungry!
挣扎在黑暗的夜中
In the night. In the dark.
他们一点也不会在乎
And they don't give a shit!
当我们病了
Then when we get sick,
制药公司就发了大财
the pharmaceutical companies make billions!
该死的医院是他们开的
They own the fucking hospitals.
挣得盆满钵盈
Filled to the brim.
太平间也是他们的
They own the morgues!
尸体防腐液也是他们的
They own the embalming fluids!
停尸房  墓地都是他们的
They own the mortuaries, the graveyards!
这些混蛋
These fucks!
我们要和谁结婚关政府什么屁事
Is it the government's business who we marry?
我们还他妈在乎
What the fuck do we care
政府对我们要和谁结婚有什么意见
what the government thinks about who we marry?
我们要请他们来参加婚礼吗
Are we gonna invite them to the wedding?
当然不
Fuck no!
反正他们也不会来的
Oh, they wouldn't come anyway.
他们...他们忙着压榨百姓
They're-they're too busy fucking!
在杂货店压榨我们
Fucking us at the grocery store!
在银行
At the bank!
在加油站
At the gas pump!
他们为我们的孩子吃有化学成分的糖果
They're feeding our children chemical shit coated in sugar!
为什么这群禽兽
Why don't these monsters
不买这些可口小吃
bite into those tasty treats themselves?
因为他们会死在大街上
Cause they'll die in the streets!
就像我们百姓一样
Just like us!
然后他们就会肿胀成一个红色气球
And then they'll bloat like a big red fucking balloon.
停下来
Stop!
别让这些屁话分散你们的注意力
Stop distracting yourself with all this diverting bullshit,
火力全开集中注意
and pay attention.
拯救孩子
Save the children!
每个父母都想救他们的孩子
Every parent wants to save their child.
自己想办法
Buy yourself a shovel,
把自己从这困境中救出来
dig yourself out of the shit,
而且要多读书
and get educated!
他真是英明
Oh, he's so beautiful.
桑尼·吉姆
Sonny Jim,
你先上车
go get in the car.
我一直在回味昨晚的事
I can't stop thinking about last night.
你真是棒极了
You're so wonderful.
棒极了
Wonderful.
我只是很想跟你分享
I just had to tell you that.
好了  先送你去上班
Okay. Let's get you to work.
你可不能骗我
You can't fool me!
我以前来过这里
I've been here before!
双峰镇警察局
你在这做什么  查德
What are you doing up here, Chad?
我...在想今天天气真好  露西
I'm... thinking what a beautiful day it is, Lucy.
我猜你是那种喜欢好天气的女生
I'll bet you're a girl who appreciates a beautiful day.
我猜你跟安迪每天醒来后会说
I bet you and Andy wake up each morning and say,
"今天天气真好啊"
"Oh, what a beautiful day it is."
那要看看我们几点起床
That depends on what time it is.
我意思是
I mean,
有时都没时间给我们去想事情
sometimes there's not even enough time to think of anything.
有一次  安迪还以为钟停了
One time, Andy was even thinking that the clock had stopped,
后来我们才意识到我们连几点都不知道
and then we realized that we didn't even know what time it was.
好像时间停住了一样
It seemed like forever.
当...
When--
我要出去了  露西
I'm going out, Lucy.
我...我看邮差来了  我去收一下信
I-I see the mailman. I'm gonna collect the mail.
他会拿进来的
But he'll bring it in.
我出去吧  不用麻烦他了
Well, I'm gonna save him the trouble
顺便享受一下这好天气
and go out and enjoy this beautiful day.
非常感谢你
Ah, thank you so much.
华盛顿州双峰镇  主街  双峰镇警察局
美好的一天
Beautiful day.
需要再来一个甜甜圈
This calls for another doughnut.
已搞定
你好  约翰尼  你今天好吗
Hello, Johnny. How are you today?
霍恩女士吗
Uh, Mrs. Horne?
你的孙子  理查德  他进来了
Your grandson, Richard, is on his way in.
你好  约翰尼  你今天好吗
Hello, Johnny. How are you today?
你休想下车  理查德
Don't even think of getting out of your car, Richard.
-来看看你  祖母  -走开
- Came to see you, Grandma. - Stay away!
-否则我报警了  -得了吧  祖母
- Or I'll call the sheriff! - Come on, Grandma.
别  别过来
No! Stop it!
我只想来要点钱
I just want a couple of dollars.
休想
No!
只要一点钱
Just want a couple of dollars.
没有  去问问你的祖父
No. Go ask your grandfather.
他一分都不会给你的  知道吗
He won't give you any more, will he?
你好  约翰尼  你今天好吗
Hello, Johnny. How are you today?
我有钱  但我想要更多
I got money, but I want more.
你一直都像我离开小镇  对吗
You always wanted me to leave town, right?
那给我钱  我就马上离开
So help me out, and I'll be out of here.
别再过来了  理查德  我说真的
Don't come any closer, Richard. I mean it.
-给我钱  祖母  -不给
- Money, Grandma! - No!
你好  约翰尼  你今天好吗
Hello, Johnny. How are you today?
约翰尼
Oh, Johnny!
你好  约翰尼
Hello, Johnny.
我  我要把你掐得屎尿齐流  臭婆娘
I... I will squeeze the shit out of you, bitch!
你今天好吗
How are you today?
你个下流贱货
You cocksucking bitch!
我还要操了那个废物
And I'll cornhole that piece of shit!
快把钱给我拿出来
Now give me some fucking money!
在我包里
In-in my purse!
不要你的包  贱货
Not your purse, bitch!
保险箱  密码
The safe. The combination.
密码给我
The combination!
-你干了什么  -什么
- What did you do? - What?
-4...  -他妈的说大声点
- Four... - What? Fucking speak up.
老子听不懂你说的半个字
I cannot understand a fucking thing you're saying.
9  0
Nine... zero...
-4  -你好  约翰尼  你今天好吗
- four... - Hello, Johnny. How are you today?
...seven.
-待在那  -你好  约翰尼
- Stay there! - Hello, Johnny.
你今天好吗
How are you today?
你好  约翰尼  你今天好吗
Hello, Johnny. How are you today?
约翰尼
Oh, Johnny.
你好  约翰尼  你今天好吗
Hello, Johnny. How are you today?
对不起
I'm so sorry.
-你看看你  -你今天好吗
- Look at you. - How are you today?
-我们别惹他生气  -你今天好吗
- We can't make him mad. - How are you today?
你好  约翰尼  你今天好吗
Hello, Johnny. How are you today?
天啊
Oh, my God.
你好  约翰尼  你今天好吗
Hello, Johnny. How are you today?
约翰尼
Johnny...
你好  约翰尼  你今天好吗
Hello, Johnny. How are you today?
没错
Yeah.
我要拿走你的包
Yeah, I will take your purse.
-还有  -你好  约翰尼  你今天好吗
- Here. - Hello, Johnny. How are you today?
这么简单的事你非要搞那么复杂
Why you have to make something so simple so fucking difficult?
臭婊子
Cunt.
你好  约翰尼  你今天好吗
Hello, Johnny. How are you today?
约翰尼  约翰尼
Oh, Johnny. Oh, Johnny.
你好  约翰尼  你今天好吗
Hello, Johnny. How are you today?
是真的
It's true.
新闻都在播
It's all over the news.
他们逮到艾克了
They got Ike.
好
Okay.
谢谢  罗杰
Thank you, Roger.
安东尼  过来
Anthony, come here.
别坐下  安东尼
Don't sit down, Anthony.
安东尼  我找你来
Anthony, I asked you here
因为你点子多
because you're a creative individual,
而接下来我要告诉你的事
and you're gonna need every ounce of that creativity
需要你发挥所有的创造力
to do what I'm about to tell you.
什么事  托德先生
What's that, Mr. Todd?
还记得我的死对头竞争对手
Do you recall my business rivals and bitter enemies
米彻姆兄弟吗
the Mitchum brothers?
你要去拜访他们
You're gonna visit the brothers now.
你要去把他们申请保险理赔
You're gonna pin the blame for the insurance claim
被我们合谋拒赔
that we conspired to deny for them,
害他们惨痛损失三千万的事
a loss of 30 million that hit 'em hard,
全赖在道格拉斯·琼斯头上
on the back of Douglas Jones.
你要说服他们
You're gonna convince them
琼斯先生对他们兄弟俩怀恨在心  私人恩怨
that Mr. Jones has it out for the brothers, a personal vendetta,
接着我们就坐等好戏上场
and then we're gonna sit back, and we're gonna watch
看米彻姆兄弟帮我们解决琼斯先生这个麻烦
as the Mitchum brothers take care of our Mr. Jones problem.
-万一...  -不说了  安东尼
- But what if-- - Don't speak, Anthony.
如果你不能成功
If you fail to deliver on this,
那你就得亲自杀了琼斯先生
then you'll have to kill Mr. Jones yourself.
梅费尔酒店
艾伯特和停尸间的女士
Albert and the lady from the morgue.
-真甜蜜  -很甜蜜
- Sweet. - Sweet.
是  是  我
Yes. Yes, I...
走吧
Come on.
银色野马赌场
他来干什么
What's he want?
-谁  -保险公司的混蛋
- Who? - That insurance fuck.
现在是后半夜了
It's after midnight.
这个畜生
The bastard.
要我相信那混蛋  还不如把车扔了
I could throw a car farther than I'd trust that rat fuck.
安东尼·辛克莱想见你
Anthony Sinclair here to see you.
留在那别动
Stay put.
我们去带他过来
We'll come get him.
坎迪
Candie.
坎迪  去把他带过来
Candie, go get him.
坎迪
Candie!
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
坎迪  去把他带过来
Candie, go get him.
你要我把他带到这来吗
You want me to bring him here?
对
Yeah.
他刚说什么了
What did he just say?
你要我去找他把他带到这来
You want me to get him and bring him here?
搞什么
What the fuck?
我们让她跟他讲故事了吗
Did we ask her to tell him her life story?
讲了该死的整整四个小时
For four fuckin' hours?
沃里克
Warrick?
让坎迪过来  跟他一起  马上
Send Candie in here, with him, now.
马上
Now!
坎迪
Candie.
他们准备好了
They're ready.
她过去了
She's on her way.
-我知道  -如果我们开除她
- I know. - We fire her,
-她就没地方去了  -我知道
- she's got no place to go. - I know. I...
他来了
Here he is.
你俩刚刚才扯什么淡
What the fuck were you guys talking about?
是她在说
She was talking.
坎迪
Candie?
你刚刚在大厅跟他说什么了
What were you talking about to him out there on the floor?
坎迪
Candie!
我们处于交替期
That we're in the version layer,
明天会雾大且炎热
that it's gonna be hot and smoggy tomorrow,
我告诉他  我们很幸运
and I told him that we are so lucky
我们的赌场有空调制冷
to have air-conditioning cooling our casino.
好  保险员先生  你有何贵干
Okay. Mr. Insurance Man, what do you want?
米彻姆先生
Mr. Mitchum.
我来告诉你们一件
I'm here to tell you something
你们会想知道的事情
that you will want to know about.
-是吗  -什么事
- Yeah? - What's that?
你的新酒店
Your new hotel,
几个月前被烧成灰烬的那个
which burned badly down to the ground a few months back,
在正式的调查后
was ruled arson
被判定为蓄意纵火
by an official investigation.
我或许给你们卖了保险  先生们
Now, I may have sold you your policy, sirs,
但理赔这事不是我处理的
but I didn't handle the claim.
是道格拉斯·琼斯负责的
It was done by Douglas Jones,
他是我们公司的员工
who works at our firm.
道格拉斯·琼斯
Douglas Jones.
我认为我该告诉你们  私下的
I thought you should know from me, unofficially,
以我个人的名义
on my own...
琼斯先生用尽他的一切权力
...that this Mr. Jones did everything in his power
阻止你们
to prevent you gentlemen
从损失中
from getting the insurance relief
获得我认为
from the loss you suffered
你们理应获得的赔偿
that I believe to this day you deserved.
道格拉斯·琼斯
Douglas Jones
似乎对你们有私人
seems to have a personal vendetta
仇恨
against you.
他仍坚持
And he still insists
不应该支付赔偿
that that claim will never be paid out,
他会尽他所能
and he'll do everything in his power
确保你们不会获得赔偿
to make sure that it never happens.
-是吗  -是吗
- Yeah? - Is that it?
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
你有个敌人  道格拉斯·琼斯
You have an enemy in Douglas Jones.
我就是来告诉你这个的
That's what I came to tell you.
坎迪  带他出去
Candie, show him out.
坎迪
Candie!
你有个敌人  道格拉斯·琼斯
You have an enemy... in Douglas Jones.
现在我知道...白兰度的感受了
Now I know... how Brando felt.
明天找那个
Calling him tomorrow,
道格拉斯·琼斯
this Douglas Jones...
见一面
...to set up a meeting.
听你的  罗德尼
Right you are, Rodney.
-听你的  -他卷走了我们
- Right you are. - He took us...
3044万
for 30 million...
7千
447 thousand...
美元
dollars.
该死
Motherfucker.
你玩我们一次  算我们倒霉
You fuck us once, shame on us.
你耍我们两次
You fuck us twice,
算你倒霉
shame on you.
你死定了
You're dead.
没错
Yeah.
劳拉
Laura!
艾伯特
Albert.
进来
Come on in.
戴安今早11点13分手机上收到这则消息
Diane received this text on her phone on 11:13 this morning.
晚饭时的谈话气氛很活跃
"Around the dinner table, the conversation is lively."
那是在库柏逃走后收到的
Now, that came in after Cooper escaped.
定位到费城的一个信号塔  所以一开始
It pinged off a cell tower in Philly, so at first,
我以为是她的一个男朋友
I thought it was one of her boyfriends--
她好像有不少男性追求者
seems she has a stable of male suitors--
但是塔米追踪到了一个墨西哥的服务器
but Tammy traced this one back from there to a server in Mexico.
墨西哥
Mexico?
她有回复吗
Did she respond?
她发了这些高度加密的信息
She sent the following heavily encrypted message:
他们抓到了黑斯廷斯
"They have Hastings.
他会带他们去那里
He's going to take them to the site."
听起来不像是对男朋友说的
Doesn't sound like boyfriend talk.
她抱我的时候我就有所感觉
I felt it when she hugged me,
但这样一来就确认了
but this confirms it.
我们该怎么办
What should we do?
盯紧她
Keep her close.
该死
Damn.
-塔米  -戈登
- Tammy. - Gordon.
进来
Come on in.
你们还记得纽约楼顶的那个谋杀案吗
You remember the penthouse murders in New York City?
记得
Yes?
这是最开始拍下的画面中发现的
This was just found on one of the earliest cards.
戴尔
Dale!
这可不得了
This is something.
这可太不得了了
This is really something.
他组哦了什么
What did he do?
他进来袭击了我们  偷走了我所有的钱
He came in and attacked us and stole all my money!
该死
Damn it.
约翰尼没事吧
Is Johnny okay?
和往常一样一点都不关心我
No concerns for me, as usual.
你问约翰尼是什么意思  被袭击的是我
What do you mean, Johnny? It was me he attacked.
西尔维娅  我当然
Sylvia, of course
也关心你
I'm concerned about you too.
他拿走了多少钱
How much money did he take?
我保险箱里的所有东西
Everything I had in the safe,
有好几千
thousands of dollars,
你要补偿我
and you're going to make this up to me.
不  我不会再给你钱了  西尔维娅
No, I am not sending you any more money, Sylvia!
你要给我
Yes, you are!
-西尔维娅  -你要给我
- Sylvia! - Yes, you are.
我现在就打给我的律师
I'm calling my lawyer right now.
贝弗莉
Beverly?
要和我一起吃晚餐吗
Do you want to have dinner with me?
霍克
Hawk.
电流在涌动
Electricity is humming.
你能在山间水边听到
You hear it in the mountains and rivers.
你能看到它在海边  在星星上
You see it dance among the seas and stars
在月亮上闪耀
and glowing around the moon,
但是最近
but in these days,
亮光越来越弱了
the glow is dying.
剩下的黑暗中  还会有什么
What will be in the darkness that remains?
杜鲁门兄弟都是真正的男人
The Truman brothers are both true men.
他们是你的兄弟
They are your brothers.
还有其他人
And the others,
一直和你一起的好人
the good ones who have been with you.
现在轮回几乎完成了
Now the circle is almost complete.
仔细聆听  欣赏时间和空间的
Watch and listen to the dream of time
梦
and space.
现在都将涌现  如同一条河流
It all comes out now, flowing like a river.
不管存不存在
That which is and is not.
霍克
Hawk.
是劳拉
Laura is the one.
枪炮酒吧
*我的梦*
*My dream*
*是去往*
*Is to go*
*那个地方*
*To that place*
*你知道是哪里*
*You know the one.*
*一切都开始在*
*Where it all began*
*一个星空之夜*
*On a starry night*
*一切都开始*
*Where it all began*
*你说过*
*You said*
*抱着我*
*Hold me*
*别害怕*
*Don't be afraid*
*我们和*
*We're with*
*星星一起*
*The stars*
*我在*
*I saw*
*你眼中看到*
*Them in your eyes*
*在一个星空之夜*
*Under a starry night*
*很久以前*
*Long ago*
*但现在*
*But now*
*这是个梦*
*It's a dream*
*没有星星*
*No stars*
*没有*
*No*
*星星*
*Stars*